pcbooster.com 2018-02-19

# Privacy Policy | PC Booster Offical Site

## **Privacy Policy**

## **General Privacy Policies**

We highly respect your interest in your own privacy and for that reason we have made this specific informational disclosure.

We gather and make use of private information for various purposes which include, but are not restricted to product and services satisfaction; billing; to deliver a much better website; to understand the needs of our customer better; to help communicate with clients and potential prospects about our product and services along with other third party product and services.

Basically, your personal information will be disclosed only to our proprietors, consultants, attorneys, partners, business associates, subsidiaries, independent contractors, employees, affiliates, suppliers, agent, and service providers, working on our request or behalf. These standard guidelines, along with disclosures within certain situations, are more specifically described below.

## **Information Gathered by our own ISP**

The Web hosting provider for this particular Internet site (along with other Internet site) has the capability to record a variety of information such as pages accessed, web browser type, domain name, computer operating system, referring information, and also to disclose this details. This is usually done by giving entry to raw server records. To find out more you need to conduct an Internet search about “raw server logs” and “server logs”. We may gain access to the “raw server logs” as well as gain access to the reports presented by our web hosting provider.

## **  Financial Information intended for Billing Purposes**

We are selling various product and services. Whenever sales are produced, financial information may be disclosed. This kind of information may include a variety of facts you’re asked to produce, but mostly involves your name, email address, billing address, and financial or credit card details. Typically, this particular purchase information will likely be supplied by you towards an authorized third party transaction processor and we don’t receive your credit card or financial information.

In case we receive your credit card or financial information, we won’t reveal it to anyone not unless disclosure is needed by a court order or by law, or until disclosure is necessary to address a certain issue involved by your financial transaction. If ever you will declare that your financial details were used in order to make any purchase that you didn’t authorize, then information about that specific financial transaction can be disclosed to any law enforcement authorities or to anybody else we consider essential to address the issue.

## **Use of E-mail Addresses and any other Contact Details**

An essential component of our services involves the ability to supply information to all of you. Because of this, you exclusively consent to obtaining communications coming from us through telephone, email, fax, mails, and any other method of delivery.

As our customer you’re agreeing to obtain information from us about the product or services that you purchased. This could include things, but not restricted to new features, service or product updates, and any other information that we think you may also find interesting.

We might also send you other information about our other products or services that our company provides.

We will never provide, transfer, or sell your e-mail address to others.

We might also allow advertisings to our clients, or participate in some joint ventures, which may result to receiving different advertisements from chosen third parties.

## **Identification of Consumers**

In the event that you buy one of our products and use any of our services, you are authorizing us to make use of your own name and other identification details on our promotions and advertising.

We can also use private information in a collective form for marketing, operational, business analysis, and any other promotional reasons.

## **Cookies**

Cookies may be utilized in order to monitor on the referred affiliate income and to keep track of any access to our site. You permit to potential use of the cookies for assessment purposes and also using cookies to publicly obtainable data to collect statistics for identifying which keywords, search engines, referring sites, bringing visitors to our site, what type of web browsers they are using, and which specific page that visitors are more interested with. Several providers may be utilized for this specific purpose.

Cookies may also be used for remarketing of our services that you may see on third party advertising networks. These cookies are used to serve our ads based upon your past visit to our website.  You can opt out by visiting Google [Ad setting](http://www.google.com/settings/ads)s or you can opt out of third party vendors at [Network Advertising](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp) Initiative opt-out page or DoubleClick’s [opt out page](https://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb#display_optout)

## **Disclosure by Necessity**

Personal Information can be disclosed if needed by statute, court order, regulation, or law.

Information can be subject to a disclosure to deal with a claim that you’re violating any term of an agreement associated with the use of our website, products, any of our services, or the rights of our third party.

Information can also be subjected to any disclosure if we think that disclosure is needed to contact, identify, or take actions against anybody who causes injury or even interfering either unintentionally or intentionally with our property and rights, your property and rights, to the other users of our site, to certain products and services, or to anyone else.

As we continuously improve our business, we and also our affiliates may buy or sell other entities or business, be purchased by any other company, or be merged with other company. In such transaction, private information may also be included on our transferred assets.

Your personal information may be kept and processed on any country which we maintain our facilities or perform our operations. By using our products, services, and website, you consent us to any transfer of information outside your country.

Immediately after you accounts are inactive, all your personal information may stay on our computers, archives, and databases, and may not fairly be expunged.

## **Policy Changes**

These policies can be amended by us anytime and without prior notice, but such changes will be listed at this page. You agree your continuing use of our products, services, and website after that specific date will constitute the acceptance and permission of the amendment.

**Effective Date: May 2013**
